<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Jekyll Template for Blogging</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 16:18:25 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 16:18:25 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bistro Vendome, Denver, CO</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Bistro Vendome is a lovely little French restaurant located down a petite rue off of Larimer St. in downtown Denver.  This quaint spot is decorated just like a small French bistro, with lace curtains, a daily blackboard, small conversational tables, and an outdoor patio.  At dinnertime, a baguette is brought to your table in a little paper bag, and water is kept in your water glasses poured from empty wine bottles.  Many of the staff have French accents, or speak fluent French.  Give them a try, if you can!  All the food here is good.  For dinner, they have a small but thorough menu, offering a satisfactory variety of French fish, poultry, and meat dishes.  All delicious, I promise!  Their wine list is equally French, and the staff is knowledgeable and willing to give you a recommendation based on value (which can be important, unless you have your heart set on an authentic Bordeaux, which they will tell you can be overpriced).  Speaking of wine, they have been offering ½-off all bottles for Saturday and Sunday brunch, and Sunday and Monday dinners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite meal at Bistro Vendome always starts with the French Onion Soup, which is a nice cup size for a starter with a flavorful broth, and all the best broiled gruyere you could possibly want.  The steak frites is my go-to entrée.  There are three sauces from which to choose—bearnaise, au poivre, and Roquefort.  The steak is a flatiron—go figure—but beautifully seared, and I love the béarnaise for my own personal taste.  The side is this cute cone of beautiful shoestring fried potatoes.  What is that different, deliciousness that makes them so crispy?  Sugar!  It is to die for.  However, if you are like my son, and prefer not to mess with your French fries, they can make them the traditional way for you.  Instead of ketchup, a nice garlic aioli is provided, which matches superbly with the steak and the frites.  Yum!  Desserts change frequently, and all are good.  It’s hard to pass on the Crème Brulee when you are at a French restaurant, and you won’t be disappointed.  Don’t forget the French press coffee for one or for the table.  Oh, and I forgot to mention that they have a full bar.  This can come in handy both before and after your glass or bottle of wine with dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This particular visit, on February 17th, found us celebrating brunch on Valentine’s Day weekend, when they specifically advertised ½-off all champagnes.  You can see from the picture I’ve posted that the champagne we discovered this lovely morning was unusual.  It was as good or better than a Dom Perignon, with that dryness and toasty, yeasty finish one has such a hard time finding except in the most exceptional of champagnes or sparkling wines.  We were seated on the side of the restaurant that has little bay windows which look out onto a rue, which is the entryway to the restaurant.  It is a cute cobblestone-ish path which adds perfectly to the bistro ambiance.  We have not visited this restaurant for brunch nearly as many times as for dinner, but maybe it should become a habit.  We got a parking spot right outside the restaurant, on Larimer (I know, right?!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our server helped us order the Louis Roederer 2006 Brut Natur.  We were looking for something we can’t get anywhere else, and this fit the bill.  It was the perfect aperitif and accompaniment to our meal.  Our server recommended the daily crepe, which was a beef bourguignon crepe with an egg on top, as well as the banana creme crepe with Nutella for dessert.  While tempting, we decided to start with the beignets.  For our meal, my husband ordered the Pain Perdu, and I the special quiche of the day, and we ordered a side of bacon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The beignets were little fried pieces of heaven, dusted with powdered sugar and too hot to touch, just as they should be–a must-have!  The bacon melted in our mouths.  The special quiche was chorizo chive with hollandaise and a side salad.  This quiche was very tall, and the most creamy, tender, eggy mixture I’ve ever had.  The side salad was fresh, light, and tangy, and a nice break from the richness of the quiche.  The pan perdu as served with lemon chiffon and shaved almonds.  It was made with a thick brioche.  The custard made the dish airy, creamy and delicious.  The sweet lemon chiffon on top was a nice touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been a couple of months since this visit, and in the meantime, we have attended several of their wine region paring dinners, and one of their movie nights.  These fixed menus are a great value, and lots of fun!  The regional dinners are finished for now, but I hope they start anew.  Keep your eyes open for them!  Their movie nights tend to be offered monthly.  There isn’t a bad seat in the house, so if they offer a movie you want to see, I highly recommend the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bistro Vendome is in the Dining Out card deck, so don’t forget to bring your card for $10 off your meal!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/04/26/Bistro-Vendome.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/04/26/Bistro-Vendome.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zolo Grill, Boulder, CO</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Zolo Grill.  Now here’s a restaurant with which I’m familiar.  I LOVE Zolo Grill!  In fact, I love all the Big Red F restaurants.  Over the years, many of the Big Red F restaurants have participated in the Dining Deck, as well as the Eat Denver discount book.   Our family has made Zolo’s our go-to place when we have an event or celebration in Boulder, CO.  It is located in a shopping area off of Arapahoe Rd. in Boulder, right next to the McGuckin’s Hardware store–a mainstay of the Boulder community for over 30 years.  A small, quality children’s furniture store used to be located right behind Zolo; I forget what it’s name was, as it’s long gone, but both my sons’ nursery furniture, and many baby items were purchased from this wonderful little shop.  But, I digress…  Did I mention that I also love Boulder?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As my younger son is studying French Horn Performance at CU Boulder, we are fortunate to attend as many of his band concerts, recitals, etc. as we are able.  February 7th, 2019 was his first Symphonic Band concert of this new semester.  My son had hoped we could meet him before the concert and have dinner with him, undoubtedly at Zolo’s, however, coming from work across town typically makes this impossible.  The proximity of Zolo to the University makes it easy to hop down for dinner at most any time.  Therefore, my husband and I made reservations for 8:45, after the concert, planning to figure out whether we share appetizers or eat a full multi-course dinner, depending on our whim when we arrived.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zolo Grill has a fantastic Happy Hour, if you can make it.  It’s a bit early, I think ending at 6:00pm during the week.  But, the bites are wonderful; and you can get smaller bites for good prices, as well as some wonderful cocktails, if you can get there before it ends.  This is a southwestern grill, and there are many New Mexican food favorites to consider.  Our favorites include a Sombre Mezcal “margarita”, called the Campfire.  There are also several choices of margaritas, both coin-style or not, and a wide selection of tequilas including flight choices.  There are quality cocktail choices on the happy hour menu (not all margaritas, either) which can be paired with salsas, guacamole, chicken wings, ribs, and bacon-wrapped dates (wow!), as an example of the available tasty bites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, February 7th was not going to be a Happy Hour value meal for us, arriving at 8:45pm, but the team always happily ushers us in and does not rush us as we enjoy our respite somewhat past the time when most of the guests have gone, with the exception of one or two parties in the bar.  The menu changes frequently, with the most popular items continuing as mainstays, e.g., the smoked chicken enchiladas.  Tonight, there were two new dinner items, and some appetizer items, that we just couldn’t pass up–Crispy Fried Anaheim Chile, Crunchy Duck Wings, Grilled Skirt Steak Skewers, and Texas Style Smokey Pork Ribs.  Well, there wasn’t enough time, nor room in our tummies, to take care of all of that food, so we will have to return before the Winter Menu expires!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started with the traditional chips and salsa, and house made guacamole.  The salsa is not too spicy, although sometimes they have a trio on the menu that has a very spicy habenero option.  This house salsa is nice and roasted, slightly sweet, with a bit of bite.  The guacamole is perfect, with fresh avocado, tomato, onion, garlic, sprinkle of chile powder.  The chips are freshly fried, warm, and lightly salted.  When my son is able to join us, he can’t stop eating these.  They just keep bringing us basket after basket, as I notice in wonder that he is still capable of later finishing an entree.  My husband chose his favorite Campfire cocktail, and I my go-to Casa Noble Reposado Coin-Style Margarita (with no salt–this is very important!).  You must ask for a straw, which comes in paper form.  Again, not my favorite thing, but I endure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my meal, I decided to go lighter by choosing the Crispy Fried Anaheim Chile appetizer along with the cast iron pan of blue corn bread (intending to share).  The dish was touted to me as a cheesy chile relleno, so I couldn’t resist.  The ribs were on my mind, but I couldn’t imagine eating so much at that moment. The chile was fine, but perhaps a bit TOO crispy.  It fell apart when cut, and there was not quite enough cheese inside.  Still, enjoyable.  The blue corn bread is one of their mainstays, but we had never ordered it before.  This comes warm in a cast iron pan, with a small tub of smoked salt honey butter.  The cornbread is soft, warm, blue corn perfection!  LOVE LOVE LOVE, and will have to be a permanent side on the table whenever we return.  My husband ordered the Skirt Steak Skewer entree.  He gave me a bite or two, and it was really wonderful.  Grilled with a BBQ bacon glaze, they were cooked to medium doneness and tender, slightly sweet, delicious!  The sides of yukon potatoes and winter succotash were nice to complete the dish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Run, don’t walk, to Zolo Grill for this winter menu before it is gone (oh, but don’t worry, the next menu will be fabulous, as well).  Definitely consider Happy Hour, as it is a great deal, especially if you have the Dining Deck $10 coupon which can be used with a food purchase of $25 (I am assuming it is not blacked out during Happy Hour–hmmmm.  But not sure).  They have a very comprehensive webpage, if you want to check out the menu before you go.  I have never had a problem getting a reservation at Zolo, either, but definitely if you have a large party (or it is CU Boulder’s Parent’s weekend or graduation), you probably shouldn’t take that chance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/02/07/Zolo-Grill.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/02/07/Zolo-Grill.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Los Chigones in Colorado Mills Mall</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, and welcome to my first restaurant review!  I’m already straying from my theme of featuring restaurants from the Denver Passbook, however, several of Troy Guard’s restaurants have been featured over the years.  Los Chigones, one of Troy Guard’s super-successful restaurants in the Denver area, recently opened a new location in the Colorado Mills Mall.  The first location in Downtown Denver opened to great reviews, and as a lover of Troy Guard’s restaurants in general, I’ve been hankering to visit for a long time.  However, the Denver location is not very convenient to me, being neither close to my home nor particularly close to the Denver performing arts scene, when I so frequently find myself needing a bit to eat.  Luckily, this new location, which took over the old California Pizza Kitchen space at the Colorado Mills Mall in Lakewood/Golden, is convenient enough for me and my husband to stop in for a snack or a meal anytime we’d like.  We finally had a chance to give it a try one Saturday afternoon, January 12th, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We did not have a reservation, but I had heard this was a larger location than most Los Chigones, so we stopped in hoping to be seated.  We were seated, at our request, at a high top in the bar (I love the high tops–so comfortable for some reason).  The dining room looked a bit small, with comfortable booths and other seating options, as well as an upstairs (which was not open when we were there).  The bar area was quite ample in size, offering high tops and family style tables; and at 1:00 in the early afternoon the music was not too loud.  Large TVs were placed such that every person in the room could watch the game or show of choice.  I imagine the super bowl last weekend drew quite a crowd, given the perfect environment to experience such an event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The seating attendant, server, and bar tender were quite pleasant and helpful; since this was our first time at the joint, we had lots of questions about the menu.  This Mexican haunt was bright and cheery, with a large mural seeming to depict the “Day of the Dead”, and a menu with many cocktails and street food-type options from which to choose.  Our first order of business was exploring the margarita choices.  They offer standard margarita choices, which can be made into my preferred “coin style” or “skinny”, and all of them can be ordered in a carafe, if you intend to spend a while there with friends.  The standard margaritas include OJ in the drink; coin-style  are made with Citronage and agave, and the skinny is made only with he tequila and agave, according to the menu.  My husband and I talked to the server, and explained that we love the tartness of the coin-style, and discovered that we could choose our tequila and have the drink provided in a carafe.  We ordered Don Julio Repasado, coin-style, in a carafe.  The drink that came was quite satisfying–tart and strong (don’t you hate it when you order a margarita only to find that it tastes more like Kool-Aide than anything else?  When I get a drink like that, I can actually feel the sugar enter my bloodstream–no thank you!).  When delivered without a straw, as is common today in Denver restaurants, a paper one was provided with no question, at my request.  Hmmm.  I guess I’ll abide the paper in favor of the safety of the sea-life, but they do get so soggy after a while.  I guess I don’t drink quickly enough :).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We found many choices of salsas, which we could purchase individually, or make our own sampler.  We chose a sampler of three:  Pineapple Chipotle, Roasted Arbol, and Habenero.  We asked about spice level (we both like our food on the spicier side), and were warned about the habanero salsa.  My thought was that when I ordered my smothered chimichanga, I would want to increase the heat level of the green chile with the habenero salsa.  I find that in most places in Denver, there are very few that offer and serve very spicy food, and I LOVE a place that offers it as a choice, at least.  Frankly, all three salsas were quite spicy; I’m sure there are one or two on the menu that would be more mild for those who prefer, but I was in heaven with our choices. The pineapple chipotle was the perfect combination of sweet and smoky.  The arbol had a nice roasted accent, and the habenero’s heat level did not disappoint.  Also, the guacamole was bright and fresh, but had very large chunks of avacado, which I decided to mash up a bit more with my own fork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their menu is strong on tacos, but also offers other items like enchiladas and burritos, smothered or not.  You can “chimi” any burrito by having it fried.  My husband and I chose to split a smothered chicken chimi with fajita veggies.  The burritos come with rice and beans inside, which I have never understood.  Why burden an already starchy tortilla dish by putting rice inside of it?  Luckily, I’ve learned to ask this question, “are the beans and rice inside the tortilla, or on the side”?  Although their standard preparation is to put the rice and beans inside, they were more than happy to provide them on the side.  The meal was delish.  I was glad to have the pop of habenaro salsa and some guac to put on each chimi bite.  Although the tortilla was a bit soggy inside (perhaps needed to be fried harder), the flavors were wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los Chigones likes to offer their chocolate chip sesame cookies at the end of the meal.  We were told that we got the last two!  Yay for us!  They were the perfect (free) sweet bite to end the meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We loved Los Chigones at the Mills Mall.  The space, the people, the atmosphere, the food.  We will be back often.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/01/21/LosChigonesMills.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/01/21/LosChigonesMills.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introduction to &quot;Everyone Eat Denver!&quot;</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!  I want to introduce you to my new Blog concept.  Did anyone out there purchase the 2018-2019 Denver DiningOut PASSBOOK, or the 2019 Eat Denver Card Deck?  Or, maybe you received one as a gift during the 2018 holiday season…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Passbook is provided by DiningOut Magazine, and contains Buy One Get One (BOGO) deals for many restaurants in the Denver, CO metro area.  Practically each restaurant included in the Passbook provides both a cocktail BOGO and an entree BOGO, but they cannot both be used in the same visit.  The book was issued in summer, 2018, and the deals in this book are good through July 31, 2019.  Last summer, I found the book offered at $39.99 for two books (it was a BOGO offer).  That deal is now long gone, but Groupon will still get you one for $42 (today, at least) if you are still in the market for the book.  Retail price is labeled as $99.  Included in the book are a variety of over 100 well-known restaurants in the Denver area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2019 Eat Denver Deck is a deck of 55 cards, each providing $10 off a $25 minimum food bill at 55 different restaurants who are members of the EatDenver restaurant association.  These cards can be used through December 31st, 2019.  You can buy the decks at venues around town, or online for about $55.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I intend to visit one of these restaurants each week and write about it, with the hope that my experiences will inspire others to eat out in Denver, and help others choose which restaurants they would like to try.  If I can, II will also provide reviews of other restaurants that are not included the book or the deck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope some of you will join me on a tour of Denver, CO restaurant experiences!  Let’s all Eat Denver!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/20/Introduction.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/20/Introduction.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who is Amanda Lucy and why does she care about the Denver Restaurant Scene?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Amanda Lucy has been interested in baking, and later, cooking, since a young age.  As a teenager, she used to make all of the desserts for her family of five, and sometimes other meals.  She also has always been interested in foreign travel, making several visits to Montreal and Quebec while at college in Northern NY State, and also studying overseas in London, England and Caen, France.  Whenever on travel, Amanda Lucy studies the local restaurant offerings, carefully researching and coordinating where she and her travel companions should spend their time and money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a middle-aged adult, she is now a foodie and well-versed in wine and cocktails, and has never stopped traveling.  Her passion is creating and consuming good food; she cooks at home for her family, frequently trying new techniques and recipes.  She is most adept at modifying recipes to her and her guests’ tastes, but is working toward one day being talented at creating her own dishes.  She is drawn to the fine restaurant scene, but is always up for finding the more casual venues that have something unique and delicious to offer; and there are many of both in the Denver area!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to travel and good food, Amanda Lucy’s interests include the performing arts.  Denver has a lush performing arts scene, and one of Amanda Lucy’s favorite things to do is to combine dinner and a show.  When her two sons were performing with the Colorado Children’s Chorale, Amanda Lucy had many occasions to choose a restaurant in a variety of locations across Denver (based on where a rehearsal or dress rehearsal may be taking place) to enjoy during the rehearsal time; most frequently this was at the Denver Center for Performing Arts (DCPA) right downtown.  As a many-year subscriber of the Colorado Symphony with her mother, Amanda Lucy also has had almost weekly occasions to choose a restaurant near DCPA with her mother to enjoy before a performance.  As a result, Amanda Lucy’s knowledge of the Denver restaurant scene is pretty thorough, and she is excited to share her experiences with others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look to Amanda Lucy for menu summaries, ambiance, any uniqueness about a venue, wine guidance, and some of her own thoughts on food choices and pairings.  She hopes this can become an exchange, and welcomes the thoughts and feedback of others regarding their own experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/19/Who-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/19/Who-is.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
