<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Jekyll Template for Blogging</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 18:03:50 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 18:03:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Los Chigones in Colorado Mills Mall</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, and welcome to my first restaurant review!  I’m already straying from my theme of featuring restaurants from the Denver Passbook, however, several of Troy Guard’s restaurants have been featured over the years.  Los Chigones, one of Troy Guard’s super-successful restaurants in the Denver area, recently opened a new location in the Colorado Mills Mall.  The first location in Downtown Denver opened to great reviews, and as a lover of Troy Guard’s restaurants in general, I’ve been hankering to visit for a long time.  However, the Denver location is not very convenient to me, being neither close to my home nor particularly close to the Denver performing arts scene, when I so frequently find myself needing a bit to eat.  Luckily, this new location, which took over the old California Pizza Kitchen space at the Colorado Mills Mall in Lakewood/Golden, is convenient enough for me and my husband to stop in for a snack or a meal anytime we’d like.  We finally had a chance to give it a try one Saturday afternoon, January 12th, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We did not have a reservation, but I had heard this was a larger location than most Los Chigones, so we stopped in hoping to be seated.  We were seated, at our request, at a high top in the bar (I love the high tops–so comfortable for some reason).  The dining room looked a bit small, with comfortable booths and other seating options, as well as an upstairs (which was not open when we were there).  The bar area was quite ample in size, offering high tops and family style tables; and at 1:00 in the early afternoon the music was not too loud.  Large TVs were placed such that every person in the room could watch the game or show of choice.  I imagine the super bowl last weekend drew quite a crowd, given the perfect environment to experience such an event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The seating attendant, server, and bar tender were quite pleasant and helpful; since this was our first time at the joint, we had lots of questions about the menu.  This Mexican haunt was bright and cheery, with a large mural seeming to depict the “Day of the Dead”, and a menu with many cocktails and street food-type options from which to choose.  Our first order of business was exploring the margarita choices.  They offer standard margarita choices, which can be made into my preferred “coin style” or “skinny”, and all of them can be ordered in a carafe, if you intend to spend a while there with friends.  The standard margaritas include OJ in the drink; coin-style  are made with Citronage and agave, and the skinny is made only with he tequila and agave, according to the menu.  My husband and I talked to the server, and explained that we love the tartness of the coin-style, and discovered that we could choose our tequila and have the drink provided in a carafe.  We ordered Don Julio Repasado, coin-style, in a carafe.  The drink that came was quite satisfying–tart and strong (don’t you hate it when you order a margarita only to find that it tastes more like Kool-Aide than anything else?  When I get a drink like that, I can actually feel the sugar enter my bloodstream–no thank you!).  When delivered without a straw, as is common today in Denver restaurants, a paper one was provided with no question, at my request.  Hmmm.  I guess I’ll abide the paper in favor of the safety of the sea-life, but they do get so soggy after a while.  I guess I don’t drink quickly enough :).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We found many choices of salsas, which we could purchase individually, or make our own sampler.  We chose a sampler of three:  Pineapple Chipotle, Roasted Arbol, and Habenero.  We asked about spice level (we both like our food on the spicier side), and were warned about the habanero salsa.  My thought was that when I ordered my smothered chimichanga, I would want to increase the heat level of the green chile with the habenero salsa.  I find that in most places in Denver, there are very few that offer and serve very spicy food, and I LOVE a place that offers it as a choice, at least.  Frankly, all three salsas were quite spicy; I’m sure there are one or two on the menu that would be more mild for those who prefer, but I was in heaven with our choices. The pineapple chipotle was the perfect combination of sweet and smoky.  The arbol had a nice roasted accent, and the habenero’s heat level did not disappoint.  Also, the guacamole was bright and fresh, but had very large chunks of avacado, which I decided to mash up a bit more with my own fork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their menu is strong on tacos, but also offers other items like enchiladas and burritos, smothered or not.  You can “chimi” any burrito by having it fried.  My husband and I chose to split a smothered chicken chimi with fajita veggies.  The burritos come with rice and beans inside, which I have never understood.  Why burden an already starchy tortilla dish by putting rice inside of it?  Luckily, I’ve learned to ask this question, “are the beans and rice inside the tortilla, or on the side”?  Although their standard preparation is to put the rice and beans inside, they were more than happy to provide them on the side.  The meal was delish.  I was glad to have the pop of habenaro salsa and some guac to put on each chimi bite.  Although the tortilla was a bit soggy inside (perhaps needed to be fried harder), the flavors were wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los Chigones likes to offer their chocolate chip sesame cookies at the end of the meal.  We were told that we got the last two!  Yay for us!  They were the perfect (free) sweet bite to end the meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We loved Los Chigones at the Mills Mall.  The space, the people, the atmosphere, the food.  We will be back often.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/02/10/LosChigonesMills.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/02/10/LosChigonesMills.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introduction to &quot;Everyone Eat Denver!&quot;</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!  I want to introduce you to my new Blog concept.  Did anyone out there purchase the 2018-2019 Denver DiningOut PASSBOOK, or the 2019 Eat Denver Card Deck?  Or, maybe you received one as a gift during the 2018 holiday season…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Passbook is provided by DiningOut Magazine, and contains Buy One Get One (BOGO) deals for many restaurants in the Denver, CO metro area.  Practically each restaurant included in the Passbook provides both a cocktail BOGO and an entree BOGO, but they cannot both be used in the same visit.  The book was issued in summer, 2018, and the deals in this book are good through July 31, 2019.  Last summer, I found the book offered at $39.99 for two books (it was a BOGO offer).  That deal is now long gone, but Groupon will still get you one for $42 (today, at least) if you are still in the market for the book.  Retail price is labeled as $99.  Included in the book are a variety of over 100 well-known restaurants in the Denver area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2019 Eat Denver Deck is a deck of 55 cards, each providing $10 off a $25 minimum food bill at 55 different restaurants who are members of the EatDenver restaurant association.  These cards can be used through December 31st, 2019.  You can buy the decks at venues around town, or online for about $55.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I intend to visit one of these restaurants each week and write about it, with the hope that my experiences will inspire others to eat out in Denver, and help others choose which restaurants they would like to try.  If I can, II will also provide reviews of other restaurants that are not included the book or the deck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope some of you will join me on a tour of Denver, CO restaurant experiences!  Let’s all Eat Denver!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/20/Introduction.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/20/Introduction.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who is Amanda Lucy and why does she care about the Denver Restaurant Scene?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Amanda Lucy has been interested in baking, and later, cooking, since a young age.  As a teenager, she used to make all of the desserts for her family of five, and sometimes other meals.  She also has always been interested in foreign travel, making several visits to Montreal and Quebec while at college in Northern NY State, and also studying overseas in London, England and Caen, France.  Whenever on travel, Amanda Lucy studies the local restaurant offerings, carefully researching and coordinating where she and her travel companions should spend their time and money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a middle-aged adult, she is now a foodie and well-versed in wine and cocktails, and has never stopped traveling.  Her passion is creating and consuming good food; she cooks at home for her family, frequently trying new techniques and recipes.  She is most adept at modifying recipes to her and her guests’ tastes, but is working toward one day being talented at creating her own dishes.  She is drawn to the fine restaurant scene, but is always up for finding the more casual venues that have something unique and delicious to offer; and there are many of both in the Denver area!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to travel and good food, Amanda Lucy’s interests include the performing arts.  Denver has a lush performing arts scene, and one of Amanda Lucy’s favorite things to do is to combine dinner and a show.  When her two sons were performing with the Colorado Children’s Chorale, Amanda Lucy had many occasions to choose a restaurant in a variety of locations across Denver (based on where a rehearsal or dress rehearsal may be taking place) to enjoy during the rehearsal time; most frequently this was at the Denver Center for Performing Arts (DCPA) right downtown.  As a many-year subscriber of the Colorado Symphony with her mother, Amanda Lucy also has had almost weekly occasions to choose a restaurant near DCPA with her mother to enjoy before a performance.  As a result, Amanda Lucy’s knowledge of the Denver restaurant scene is pretty thorough, and she is excited to share her experiences with others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look to Amanda Lucy for menu summaries, ambiance, any uniqueness about a venue, wine guidance, and some of her own thoughts on food choices and pairings.  She hopes this can become an exchange, and welcomes the thoughts and feedback of others regarding their own experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/19/Who-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/19/Who-is.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
